cochill.net 2016-10-27

# 

USPCA Region 12 Privacy Statement
A. Overview
The United States Police Canine Association (USPCA) Region 12 is aware of and responsive to your concerns regarding
how information about you is collected, used and shared when you visit the USPCA Web site. Uspcaregion12.com is
committed to protecting the privacy of its consumers. This notice describes the Privacy Statement applicable to our Web site
("Privacy Statement"). Although the Privacy Statement is discussed in more detail below, it is important to note:1. The
personally identifiable information that you provide is considered confidential and except as otherwise explained below in
Paragraph C, such information will not be provided to others. Please note that this policy applies only to uspcaregion12.com
and not to the Web sites of other companies or organizations to which uspcaregion12.com may provide links as further
explained below in Paragraph H. By visiting, accessing, browsing or using the Web site you agree to the practices described
in the Privacy Statement.
B. The Information uspcaregion12.com Collects
Information gathered online may be referred to as either anonymous or personally identifiable information. Anonymous
information refers to Web site usage information that cannot be traced back to a specific individual, e.g., the total number of
visitors to our Web site ("General Information"). Personally identifiable information refers to specific information about a
customer, e.g., name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and credit card information. ("Personal Information").
Please note that it is your choice to share personal information via the Web site. Only consider sharing personal information
with uspcaregion12.com if you agree to our Privacy Statement.
1. General Information
Uspcaregion12.com may collect certain general information automatically, including "site usage" information from all visitors
to the Web site. Such data is used only in the aggregate. General information helps uspcaregion12.com determine general
usage patterns and modify the Web site in order to improve your experience. This type of general information may be
shared with third parties any time. Uspcaregion12.com may, at times, use a technology nicknamed "cookies" that tells
uspcaregion12.com how and when pages in our Web site are visited, and by how many people. Uspcaregion12.com cookies
do not collect personal information and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal
information to tell us who you are or even what your e-mail address is. We may also provide statistical general information to
our uspcaregion12.com advertisers as to how our customers use our Web site. The Web site may include content from other
parties that may perform user activity tracking other than that described herein. In particular, some of our third party vendors
may use "cookies" in ways that we do not.
2. Personal Information
There are times when uspcaregion12.com may specifically ask for information about you when you sign up to use a service
or when you order a product. Uspcaregion12.com may need certain personal information such as name, Internet address,
billing address, type of computer, or credit card number, in order to provide that service or product to you. We may also use
that personal information to let you know of additional products and services about which you might be interested unless you
choose not to receive such information.
C. Use and Disclosure of Information
1. How uspcaregion12.com uses the information;
You acknowledge and agree that uspcaregion12.com has the right to use personal information and general information and
any other information (collectively "Information") that uspcaregion12.com collects from or about you through its Web site.
Except as otherwise explained herein, unless uspcaregion12.com has your consent, or is required (or permitted) by law,
uspcaregion12.com will not share your information with any unaffiliated entity.
2. Who uspcaregion12.com shares your information with
Notwithstanding the above uspcaregion12.com may disclose information to (i) a uspcaregion12.com advertisers.
uspcaregion12.com may also disclose information about you to others if we have a good faith belief that we are required to
do so by law or legal process, to respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of the USPCA or others.
D. Children

Uspcaregion12.com does not sell products and services for purchase by children. If you are under 18, you may use the Web
site only with involvement of a parent or guardian. In response to concerns about protecting children's privacy online,
Congress enacted the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"). COPPA sets forth rules and procedures
governing the ways in which Web sites may collect, use and disclose any personal information regarding children under the
age of 13. Therefore, in accordance with this Privacy Statement and COPPA regulations, uspcaregion12.com does not:1.
Request or knowingly collect personal information from persons under 13 years of age ("Children"); 2. Knowingly use or
share personal information from persons under 13 years of age with third parties; 3. Give children the ability to publicly post
or otherwise distribute personal information; and 4. Entice children with the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity
to divulge personal information. Uspcaregion12.com does not knowingly collect information about children and believes that
children should get their parent's consent before giving out any personally identifiable information. We encourage you to
participate in your child's experience on the Internet and to review important safety tips with each child before he or she
explores the Internet.
E. Security Procedures
When necessary and when any type of payment or personal information other than name and email address are
transmitted, uspcaregion12.com operates secure data protected by industry standard firewall and password protection
systems. Uspcaregion12.com may also use Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") software to protect your information during
transmission. Only authorized individuals of uspcaregion12.com, who must access said information in order to provide
uspcaregion12.com products, services and customer service to you, may access the personal information.
Uspcaregion12.com makes no representations or warranties with regard to the sufficiency of these security measures.
Uspcaregion12.com shall not be responsible for any actual or consequential damages that result from a lapse in compliance
with this Privacy Statement as a result of a security breach or a technical malfunction. It is important that you protect your
any user names and passwords and not share them with others. Certain information may be transmitted to you by electronic
mail. Although it is illegal to intercept or disclose these messages under Federal law, these transmissions are not secure.
F. Applicable Law/International Issues
Because uspcaregion12.com is committed to protecting your privacy, information that is submitted to this site will be
collected, processed, stored, disclosed and disposed of in accordance with applicable U.S. law. If you are a non-U.S. user,
you acknowledge and agree that we may collect and use your personal data and disclose it to other entities, as discussed in
"Who uspcaregion12.com Shares Your Information With" above, outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, such
information may be stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction. U.S. law may not provide the degree of
protection for information that is available in other countries. By providing us with your information, you acknowledge that
you have read this Policy, understand it, agree to its terms and consent to the transfer of such information outside your
resident jurisdiction. If you do not consent to the terms of this Policy, please do not use this site.
G. How to Update or Delete your Information
Uspcaregion12.com offers you an opportunity to review the personal information provided through the Web site in order to update or correct
any errors or delete such personal information. To update or delete personal information previously provided, you may (a) email your request
to Mark McDonaugh. Email
H. Linked Internet Web sites
The Web site provides hyperlinks, which are highlighted words or pictures within a hypertext document that, when clicked,
take you to another place within the document, to another document altogether, or to other Web site not controlled by
uspcaregion12.com. These hyperlinked Web sites may contain privacy provisions that are different from those provided
herein. Uspcaregion12.com is not responsible for the collection, use, or disclosure of information collected through these
Web sites or link and uspcaregion12.com expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such collection, use, or
disclosure.
I. Changes to uspcaregion12.com Privacy Statement
If the USPCA decides to change the Privacy Statement, it will post those changes here so that you will always know what
information we collect, and how we might use or disclose that information. Any changes to this Privacy Statement will be
considered effective immediately after the changes are posted on this Web site. The Privacy Statement was last revised on
January 15, 2007.
J. How to Contact uspcaregion12.com
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, please send an Email to Mark McDonaugh
